We did it, Skye. After like eight
months, we finally found enough of the
broken glass shards to fix that broken
mural.
>> Well, it's about damn time, [__]
We're finally going to figure out who's
on this [__] Give me the glue stick.
>> No, it it can't be. Skye, is that who I
think it is? What in the world? That's
just Goku from Dragon Ball Z. Hey yo,
Brandon, we got to get the out of here.
Watch my ass while I go destroy this
[__]
>> God damn.
>> God damn it all. Hold on, Skye. I'll
rescue your fat ass.
>> Vegeta, take his ass out.
Done. Get out of my way.
>> Oh, hell no. He cut my sword with his
ass.
Now I get it. These aren't just glass
windows at all.
>> So, you finally figured it out, Skye.
Krillin, why don't you tell our friends
here what's going on?
>> I got you, [__] You see Skye? These
aren't just murals. These are also
doorways between worlds and they exist
in every possible universe. Long ago,
the doorray that connected our two
worlds was broken when I was traveling
through and accidentally farted on it,
thus sealing off our two worlds. But
because you finally repaired it, I'm
finally able to return and give you your
invitation.
>> Invitation to what, [__]
>> What else, [__] The Tournament of
Power.
The Tournament of Power is a multiversal
battle royale that will decide the fate
of your universe. You must select five
mortal warriors to fight alongside you,
forming a team of six. The losing teams
will be erased from existence along with
their universe. Refusing to participate
will result in immediate eraser. You
have 15 minutes to respond.
>> I see. It is just as I expected.
>> Bart Lebby, you knew this would happen.
Many months ago when I came face to face
with that man, I could see the look in
his eyes. It was the eyes of someone who
lusts to be locked in combat with only
the strongest warrior. It was only
natural that he would put something like
this together. Also that he could fight
me specifically because he is jealous of
my big muscles. The rest of you shall
remain here. Only I am needed to protect
our world. Hey now, don't forget we are
the Sonic Underground. Wherever there's
danger, it's the Sonic Underground's job
to answer the call.
>> Okay.
>> Sorry I took so long to get to the door,
boys. My massive tits were preventing me
from getting up off the couch. Haha. Oh,
hi, manic baby. I could barely see you
from over my mountains size boobies. Did
you come over to have sex with me?
>> Bro, what are you thinking? Inviting
her? We said no girls allowed, remember?
Hold on, [__] Your brother may just be
on to something here. Meny L has had a
[__] ton of plastic surgery done
throughout her life, so punching her is
like punching a blowup doll.
>> Haha, you boys are going to make me
blush talking about my fake tits. But it
is true though. I have so much silicone
in my butt and boobs.
>> So if anyone tries to shoot us, we can
use your girlfriend as a shield. We got
this tournament in the bag, bro.
>> Mindy, who's at the door? Invite them in
and ask if they want to play cooking
mama with me.
>> Flora, shut up.
>> Flora, go back inside.
>> Why?
>> Because this doesn't involve you. We're
recruiting Mindy for a Universal death
match. Now go inside. This is a top
secret meeting.
>> Thanks for the input, Sonic. I'll take
what you said under consideration while
continuing to do whatever I want in my
house.
>> Get lost. We don't want any chicks on
our team. Only guys with big balls.
Trevor, since when were you here? I was
here the whole time. Are you really
going to act like you guys didn't
notice?
We don't want you on our team either.
What? But but Sonic, I'm way past
school. You said it yourself. Because I
have cool hair shaped like a rocket
ship. No, I said that's why you will
never be cool.
>> You ain't cut out for this [__] nerd.
Knuckles,
>> you claim that you want to fight your
weak little man, but at the end of the
day, are you not gay? How do we know you
truly have what it takes to save the
world when you spend so many waking
hours fantasizing about Big Ball? How do
we know during the battle you won't try
and grab our own ball?
>> The Akidna speaks true. I hear Trevor is
really gay.
>> You don't even radiate the same manly
aura that we do. The way I see it,
you're more of an enemy to us than the
ones trying to destroy our world. And
I'm tired of pretending like you aren't
when you are gay.
>> Look at you, Nucks, showing up late like
you're hot [__] You're talking as if
you're already on the team.
>> You didn't think I was going to let you
do this without your rival, did you,
[__]
>> Hey, wait a minute, bro. Me, you, Mindy,
Bartleby, Flora, and Knuckles. Bro, we
have our six fighters right here, bro.
We got to put together a team that makes
our universe look super cool. And that
means no girls.
>> Yeah, Knuckles. The cool Lina isn't
fighting next to [__]
>> Okay, but counter point. Bart will be
face it, bro. We ain't doing [__]
anyway. Right now, we're just filling
out a pointless list because Bart Lebby
will hard carry us anyway.
>> I um I don't believe in violence of any
kind. Then it is decided my beach. A
universe is going to be represented by
me. The richest man alive. A man who
can't run anymore because he got fat.
His brother whose hair looks like a
pottered plant. A blowup dull looking
bingo with massive honking titties.
Autism.
>> I love white people so much. They don't
pay much attention to me because I'm
blue, which on planet Mobius is the
equivalent to being black. But I'm okay
with it because it just makes the
stalking easier.
>> And Knuckles.
I have brought the four of you here to
Chipotle because I have personally
deemed you to be the strongest Equestria
has to offer. No one here believes you.
Trixie wants that to be perfectly clear
before you begin.
>> What? You didn't pick the strongest
ponies at all. You simply picked a few
out based on color so that you could
stand in the middle in an aesthetically
pleasing way.
>> Yeah, I think Trixie is right, Twilight.
I'm worried that your lust for
leadership gave us all an early death
sentence.
>> You have quite the nerve to say that to
someone who bought you Chipotle.
>> Then why are you sitting exactly in the
middle?
>> That's where the leader sits and the
Tournament of Power letter was sent to
me, not you. Okay, but serious question,
why is there only five of us when the
letter said we could bring six? I
decided five was enough. Smaller teams
are more coordinated and efficient.
>> Liar. Sparkle is reducing our chances of
victory. Also, she can stand in the
middle. That is not true. Then let the
great and powerful Trixie in the middle.
No.
>> Yes, Pinkie Pie. I agree. If Bartleby
takes part in this tournament, it is
highly likely that we will all lose our
lives.
Twilight, another fat [__] just
walked in to stare at your bodacious
purple butt cheeks. Do you want me to
call the manager over?
>> Twilight, I need to talk to you.
>> Not now, Spike. I'm busy assembling a
team to save the universe. Don't talk to
me.
>> That's what I'm here about. I have a
secret plan. Or rather, a secret item
wedged up in my fat ass that could help
us win the tournament.
>> Okay, you can be on the team, I guess,
but stand behind me where no one can see
you so you don't throw off the whole
color scheme.
>> Okay, but I'm really small and weak, so
please protect me. You're not really
that small because you have a really big
butt crack. Just don't turn your back to
the enemy and it gives the illusion that
your ass cheeks aren't like two massive
easily targetable cinder blocks.
Krillin baby Goku is here. He said to
put your underwear and socks on and come
downstairs to greet the Z warriors that
just arrived for the ultimate battle.
Thanks for letting me know, [__] But
you're a female and I don't listen to
those things. Tell Goku I'm just going
to go poop real quick and then be down
in like 3 hours and 27 minutes. Or is
that too much for you to handle because
you're a female dumb stupid ass [__]
Goku, why is Vegeta standing next to you
instead of me? Krillin, I don't know how
to say this, but we all talked it over.
And
>> it's okay, Kakarat. I got this. To be
honest, we don't think you're strong
enough to be Goku's second in command
for the tournament, Krillin.
>> No, you're you're lying to me, Goku. You
know how hard I train. You promised you
would let me stand next to you when we
greet the warriors so that I would look
badass in front of the other universes.
I know. And that's why I respect your
ass enough to tell you to your face
instead of lie and talk [__] about you
behind your back like white women do
about their fat friends.
>> Goku, please. Come on, man. I'll I'll
suck your dragon balls.
>> Krillin, it's over. Go stand next to
Tienne, who just pooped his pants where
you belong.
>> I'm going to go behind the house to wait
until we leave. I don't have the heart
to look at my best friend who betrayed
me right now. And I definitely don't
want to stand next to someone whose
pants is covered in slimy [__]
>> QUILLIN, I'M SORRY.
>> YOU'RE NOT SORRY, VEGETA. You know
exactly what you're doing. If you
weren't so powerful and sexy, and let
Goku bang your butt, which is super gay,
by the way, Goku would still respect me.
>> You know what? MAYBE YOU'RE RIGHT. I AM
STRONG AND I AM SEXY WITH A BIG FAT ASS.
DO YOU seriously think I don't notice?
The sexual thrill Goku receives when he
is locked in combat with me. A truly
powerful Saiyan warrior. Why in God's
name do you think I wear this skin-tight
suit that hugs my butt crack? It's proof
that unlike you, I am proud of what GOD
GAVE TO ME.
>> OH, WHICH IS A FAT ASS. You're just a
bald little [__] [__] boy who hates
yourself because you can't go Super
Saiyan.
>> How is he taking it?
>> As well as a bald [__] can. My gay
lover, let's head to the battleground
and greet the warriors.
>> Prince Sky, where is the rest of your
team?
>> Oh, well, I I just like figur since
since you're going to be in the
tournament, Bobby, I was like, I don't
see the point trying. Like, we all know
you're going to win. You're like
wrenching [__]
I see. That makes sense.
>> Oh my, look at all of those big, strong
men. I wonder if they'll let me suck
their balls.
>> Welcome to the arena, contestants. This
is where we shall do battle and discover
which of our universes is truly the most
powerful. The rules are simple. Rule
number one, no killing. If you kill an
opponent, we will kill you. Rule number
two, if you are knocked off the ledge,
you are knocked out of the tournament.
When you do get knocked off the ledge,
you will be transported to the sidelines
where you will wait until the last man
is standing. Whoever wins gets one final
wish, and the losing universes will have
their own universes erased. And lastly,
for the most important rule of all,
Bartleby Montlair of Dresden cannot
enter the battlefield for 20 minutes
because we're afraid of his ass.
>> That's cheating. Without Bartleby, we're
going to lose.
>> I'm sorry. I don't remember you putting
this tournament together, fat boy.
>> Come on, Bart Lebby. Let's just go home.
>> No, my [__] We already agreed to this
tournament. But But my lover,
>> but nothing. If we turn and leave now,
we will look like God. Worse yet, our
world could face extermination.
Here is what I want you all to do. I
want you to go out there and fight.
Fight as though your life depends on it.
And show them all the power of Sonic
Underground.
>> We are going to die.
Look, someone is already trying to hide
behind that rock. Should I go over there
and force him to let me suck his fat
balls?
>> He must be a weakling. If he's running
away already, leave that guy to me.
Careful, Manic the Hedgehog. It will
most likely be a trap. Don't tell me
what to do, [__]
>> My [__] STINKS SO BAD. I WAS SURE no
one would follow me. But here you are,
manic. I knew at least one person would
be stupid enough to get lured into my
trap.
>> No, you tricked me.
>> You underestimated me and thought you
could beat my ass because I'm a [__]
But little did you know this [__] was
packing heat all along. Now back up to
the ledge before I blow your brains out.
>> You can't do that. Killing is against
the rules.
>> You think I don't know that, [__] Why
do you think I'm on the team in the
first place? Originally, Goku wasn't
going to let me because I'm weak. But I
persuaded his ass by telling him that I
have a gun and how I am willing to throw
my life away if I am able to take out at
least one of you dweebs. Now jump off
the edge if you want to live.
>> You're bluffing.
>> Does it feel like I'm bluffing, white
boy? If I have to ask you again, I'm
taking off my pants,
>> bro. I'm sorry. Krillin is just too
powerful for me.
>> So long, loser. I always win.
>> And so the first man falls. The
tournament has officially begun.
>> Bart Lebby, I'm so sorry. I failed us
all.
No, my friend. Anyone except for me
would have made the same mistake. All
that matters is that you gave it your
all and went out fighting like a bad
[__]
>> TN, focus your fire on Sonic. He can't
dodge two of our attacks at once because
he's fat.
>> Well, I may be half a mile away from the
battlefield, but the rules didn't
specify whether I could eat my [__]
from afar, did they not?
>> He He's fast. I don't understand. He
shouldn't be able to move at such a
speed because he's a fat ass.
>> It's simple, really. There's not a man
alive with an so pump. So use my beach.
>> By using these gold nuggets in my
pocket, I am able to push my [__] to
safety far beyond 900 trillion times
faster than the speed of sound.
>> How did he jump so high when he isn't
black? Whatever. Now we got you, [__]
No matter how fast you may be Sonic the
Hedgehog, even you can't dodge in
midair.
>> Diva down.
>> Now, my beach, how will you handle the
second one?
Look at you. You're adorable.
It's just as I thought, the Z warriors
brought all of the Dragon Balls with
them. Little do they know, I still have
the four-star Dragon Ball up my ass. If
I can get over there and stand next to
those six orange balls, it will resonate
with a four-star ball in my fat ass and
I'll be able to
and I'll be able to grant a wish,
putting an end to this tournament once
and for all. I will return to Ponyville
as the hero that saved the universe. Who
says sticking random [__] up your ass
doesn't pay? Screw you, Dad.
>> Kakarot, that purple dragon IS GOING TO
STEAL OUR DRAGON BALLS. USE THE DOUBLE
BARREL SHOTGUN. I'M CARRYING IN MY BUTT
CRACK AND STOP HIM.
>> OKAY, let me pull up my pants first
since I'm pooping on the ground right
now.
>> Spike, look out. Goku has figured out
what you are pling to do with the Dragon
Balls.
He got shot in the heart. He He's dead.
Goku killed him.
>> I can't believe it. The character Spike
from My Little Pony Friendship is Magic
by Hasbro is dead.
>> You monster. The rules specifically said
killing is off limits.
>> Yeah, if you're not going to follow the
rules, then why do we have to? This was
a trap all along. He's planning to kill
us all.
>> Shut. Shut up. I didn't do it on
purpose. You all saw. He was trying to
steal my dragon balls. I didn't do
anything wrong. Stay back, all of you.
Vegeta, Gohan, change of plans. We're
going to kill everyone.
Gohan, my son, let go. There's only like
3 minutes left until Bartleby enters the
arena. I am not going to lose.
>> Daddy, stop it. You're going crazy.
JESUS CHRIST. KAKAROT SHOT THE
KAMEHAMEHA OUT OF HIS HUGE FAT ASS LIKE
IT WAS A REALLY BIG FART. THAT'S THE
MOST POWERFUL FORM OF THE KAMEHAMEHA.
IT'S EVEN MORE POWERFUL THAN 20 SPIRIT
BOMBS PUT TOGETHER. AND HE DID IT RIGHT
IN GOHAN'S FACE. OH MY GOD.
>> Come on, every pony. Let's go back to
Equestria before he kills us all.
The ponies are trying to make a break
for it. Krillin, do something.
Trixie, a horse can survive on three
legs. Though it is not ideal and
presents significant life-threatening
challenges due to a horse's heavy
weight. So, I'll most likely be dead by
next week if I don't get to a hospital.
If I do bury me at the library, at least
that way I know you'll visit me. Now, do
you see what happens when you become my
enemy? Both her and that purple dragon
lost their lives because they chose not
to follow the rules that I set in place.
But don't worry, Twilight Sparkle,
because you will also be in hell
alongside her after I am done with you.
>> You see what just happened? You weren't
able to keep Trixie safe because you've
grown soft. But if you still had me, you
may have reacted sooner, fast enough to
save her. Because unlike you, I don't
second guess.
I don't make mistakes.
my mind
without me shine
every time I fall into your arms
and
you
It's true. I still love you now and
forever.
Don't matter.
All that you said has been
Jesus Christ.
about you, baby. Don't you know?
>> So, you want to fight seriously, huh?
>> Very well, My Little Pony. It's time for
me to pull out all the stops.
Look guys, Goku tapped into his most
powerful form, the Ultra Instinct. If
Krillin can kill Flawless before
Bartleby enters the arena in 10 seconds,
we'll win the tournament. Go Goku, kill
that [__]
Well, would you look at that? Going by
my 500 karat solid gold Rolex. It is
finally time to make my grand entrance
and give Gaku the fight he's always
dreamed of.
>> Hey there, Gaku. I hear you're strong.
>> That long golden hair and bulging
muscles. It's as if you're always in
Super Saiyan 3. This is going to be my
greatest battle indeed.
>> Oh, one second. I didn't notice my shoes
are untied. He's tying his shoes. Now is
my chance to cheat while he's
distracted. I'll use all of my remaining
power to destroy him before he can even
have the chance to attack me.
>> KAM.
IMPOSSIBLE. I put everything I had
behind that attack. And yet this
multi-millionaire seems totally unfazed.
Did I even hit him with it or did I
miss? I need to try it again to make
sure.
Kamibr.
>> Fine then, Bartleby. I see your power
and shall match it with my own.
>> Now the real fight begins.
>> Spaceman space
to be a spaceman.
Spaceman spaceman.
Aarweight Super Saiyan 3. He must be
jealous of Bakubi's long golden hair.
Now he's trying to rip him off.
>> [__] My friends, he is too powerful for
me. So, I am once again asking for your
support. Give me your energy so that I
don't lose like a [__]
>> Come on, guys. Let's help Goku out by
adding our power to the spirit bomb.
It pains me to aid my rival, but for the
first time in my life, I am afraid.
Afraid of Bartleby. So, Kakarok, I will
lend YOU MY POWER. DO NOT WASTE IT.
>> The king of duty is my final destin.
>> Damn it, your spirit bomb didn't do jack
[__]
>> There it is. Goku's ultimate form again.
If he can't defeat Bartleby with that
form, then nothing will. And our
universe is lost. Our victory is in your
hands, Goku. You put up a good fight,
Bartleby. But this is me at my current
strongest. My only regret is that this
battle must end for it truly was the
greatest battle I've ever been in.
>> Hurry. Bobby is almost done tying his
shoes.
Kakarot pooped himself.
All right, Gakum shoes are tied. Now we
can begin our battle.
Hey, where did he go?
>> You did it, Bartleby. You saved the
world.
>> No, my [__] You did it because you
have a fat ass.
>> Bartleby, you just proved to me, no to
everyone here, that you really are the
strongest being in the omniverse. I can
say without a doubt in my heart that I
will never be able to fight anyone as
strong or sexy as you ever again.
>> Hey now, you better take that to heart,
Bartleby, because our Goku doesn't say
that to just anybody.
>> Uh-huh. indeed I will. Now, Goku, wasn't
it you who said that the winner would
get a wish?
>> Yeah, but I'm sure there's not very many
things you could want since you're the
richest man alive.
>> Indeed, and I'm not a very materialistic
person either. However, I do have one
wish. One that I think we would all
enjoy. I wish that all of the universes
that took part in this tournament won't
get destroyed. That way, we can all
return home as new friends.
>> Bartleby, now I know why the spirit bomb
didn't harm you. Because it only harms
those with malicious hearts. And your
heart is more pure than anyone I have
ever met.
>> Well, since Spike is dead, I think we
should let Sparky know. They were best
friends after all.
>> You're probably right. I'll tell him.
Hey, Sparky.
>> Who is this?
>> It's the great and powerful Trixie.
>> I don't know who that is. Talk fast. I
got hamburger helper on the stove.
>> Well, I hate to break this news with you
over the phone, but Spike is dead.
>> Oh my god. How did he die?
>> Did anyone else actually see what
happened? I didn't get a good look. It's
kind of hard to explain, BUT IN SHORT,
SPIKE WENT FOR OUR balls and and I had a
double barrel shotgun in my ass. Kakarot
pulled the shotgun from my rear. And I I
swear I didn't tell him to do it, but
when Kakarot gets going, nothing can
stop him. Well, Sparky, the fact of the
matter is Spike was shot dead at
Kakarot's feet. I am so sorry. God, I'm
sorry.
Come on, Flawless. We're going home.
>> May I please have another hot dog?
>> Come on, Sonic. You already had six. You
already take wieners up the ass. Do you
really NEED MORE FOR YOUR MOUTH? Let
some other fighters have some wieners.
Stop hoarding the burgers for yourself,
fatty.
>> No, I don't think I will.
>> Dude, come on. You have like 12 burgers.
>> Piss off. I require more hamburgers than
anyone else to sustain my perfection.
>> This is getting weird. Usually, she's
moderately tolerable. But ever since we
got back home, she has been stealing
burgers and potato salad, claiming it's
all hers. When the hell did Flawless
turn into a massive [__]
I probably should have told you sooner,
but months ago, I performed an
extraction spell on her that removed the
concentrated darkness in her heart, but
it seems to have crept its way back to
her.
>> What do you think you're doing?
>> I'm pouring myself a glass of lemonade.
Would you like me to pour one for you?
>> No. You will immediately surrender the
citrus drink to me.
>> Oh, yeah. That's That's exactly what I
was going to do, Miss Flawless. Please
don't hurt me. Cool it you too. Remember
friendship is magic and friendship means
sharing. Sharing would imply equality
which defies logic as I am the most
superior life form at this backyard
cookout. Is this not an observable data?
Floral lour. Give me the lemonade. Look
at her crying. She struggles with basic
converse. Why is she here? That lemonade
belongs in more capable hooves.
>> Flaw sparkle moon. Leave the mentally
stunted blue pixie alien creature alone.
Clearly, she is feeling uncomfortable
and you are scaring her.
>> Nice going, Twilight Sparkle. Your kid
made a Sonic underground character cry.
There's a special place in hell for
people who do that sort of [__]
>> Flawless, you're going in timeout. Go
sit in the timeout corner with Pinkie
Pie and Krillin from Dragon Ball Z. And
after you do that, I want you to go over
there and apologize to that poor girl.
No, it was her decision to cry.
What is that? Oh, hello again, Flawless.
I'm just writing in my notebook about
the adventures I had today. Is that a
fluffy animal notebook? I think you
should give that to me and then un alive
yourself.
Here's your hot dog, baby. The great and
powerful Trixie made it just how you
like it. A tablespoon of relish and a
little squirt of mayo.
>> I didn't see mayo on the table.
>> Watch yourselves, everyone. IT COULD BE
A NEW ENEMY.
>> Don't be alarmed, every pony. This is
just the national show mayare mascot
likely to reinstate the great and
powerful Trixie back into the National
Show Association after showing off an
impressive display at the Tournament of
Power. Trixie Lulleoon, you have
continued hosting magical exhibitions
for financial gain despite official
disapproval. For committing this act,
you have violated a major performance
sanction. Your magic privileges are
hereby revoked. Further casting of
spells of any kind will result in your
immediate extermination.
>> Trixie can't use magic anymore. No magic
at all. Further casting of spells of any
kind will result in your immediate
extermination.
Twilight Sparkle, you cannot intervene.
>> Well, see about that. I'm taking you to
someone else who has a higher
jurisdiction over unicorn magic than you
ever could.
Twilight, wherever did you find that
thing?
>> It's been appearing before Trixie every
now and then, and it claims it has the
power to like revoke her magic license
or something. I was wondering if you
could explain it to me. It's like an
enchanted doll, but whatever spell I
try, I can't seem to crack it. I was
hoping you could do something about it.
>> I'm afraid I cannot, Twilight.
>> What? Why?
>> Because it isn't an enchanted artifact
at all. It's a flesh and blood creature,
and it's only pretending to be a toy.
Like some weird fetish. It certainly is
a curious little pony, isn't it?
>> I've never seen a pony like it before.
What even is it?
>> You see, a long time ago, there was once
a girl who lived in an orphanage who had
a really fat butt. And she desired to
see the world. An Earth pony named
Skywishes. She had two notable friends.
One of them was a young jester colt
named Trixie Bell. He was dropped off at
the orphanage by a circus troop called
the caravan of cackling horses because
he was really, really ugly. And nobody
liked hanging around him because he
smelled like popcorn. But Skywishes did
like popcorn. So, the two of them were
instantly inseparable and they grew up
like a real brother and sister would.
And then there was Starcatcher, an
astral pony that supposedly came to
Equestria from outer space. Starcatcher
was much older than the other two
because she had already been fully grown
by the time they started living in the
orphanage. She was like a caretaker to
them and the other children. But things
started to change over time and everyone
could see it that Trixie Bell was in
love with Skywishes. He believed that
one day she would eventually see him the
same way. But Skywish's heart already
belonged to another because she was
really, really gay. Skywishes was in
love with Starcatcher. But unlike Trixie
Bell, Skywishes didn't cling to
unobtainable desires. Once she was old
enough, she figured it was time to leave
the orphanage. She hugged her two
friends goodbye, and that was when
Trixie Bell saw it. The way Skywish's
eyes softened whenever she looked at
her. In that moment, the jester knew
that her future did not include him the
way he had imagined. To Trixie Bell, he
lost a sister, friend, and lover
allinone. Fueled by heartbreak, the now
grownup jester turned against his
friend, Star Catcher.
>> All women are queen.
>> IF SHE BREATHES, SHE'S A THOUGHT.
>> What began as one man's desperate act
eventually became a cataclysm that
engulfed the world. Pony Kind was
brought to near extinction, but
Starcatcher studied the way of the
blade, which made her really strong. And
she cut her love rival in half with her
authentic $18 katana that she got off of
teu.com.
>> Damn. What happened to Sky Wishes?
>> No one knows for certain, but they say
Skywishes walked through the ruins after
the battlefield and found Trixie Bell as
he lay dying. Even if she couldn't
forgive what he did to the planet, she
still cared for the man who had shared
her childhood, and she placed his
favorite plush toy in his hooves. Over
centuries, whispers persist that the
doll instead became a vessel, and Trixie
Bell's spirit bound itself to it in his
final moments over the fear of death.
Because all straight ponies go to hell.
As it turns out, gay ponies like
Skywishes are reborn again as ponies,
forced to live in Equestria as a pony
for all eternity. A fate far worse than
hell because they are a pony.
>> The food at this cookout sucks.
>> What do you expect WHEN IT'S A BUNCH OF
WHITE PEOPLE? The only good thing was
that cornbread Piccolo brought cuz he's
like a black guy. Hey, wait here. I want
to go ask Mindy if I can touch her
boobs.
>> My brother in Christ, she's way out of
your league. Yeah. Also, you wear an
adult diaper.
>> NOT BECAUSE I NEED IT. IT'S DIFFERENT
WHEN IT'S A FETISH.
>> DAMN. VEGETA, calm your tits. I'm just
messing with
>> No, I WILL NOT CALM DOWN. I AM THE
PRINCE OF ALL SAIYANS, AND I WILL NOT BE
TALKED DOWN TO BY A LOWERASS SAIYAN
WARRIOR.
>> Gather around, everyone. My [__] wants
to take a commemorative photo.
>> I don't want to. You might want to
celebrate, but that's only because you
won. The rest of us are losers.
Yeah. Do you know what it's like to have
your universe on the brink of
destruction? We had to live in fear the
whole time because we knew you were in
the battle.
>> I'll take a picture with you, Sonic.
>> You will?
>> Yeah. And so will I. I don't see why
not. If I get to stand next to a hot
piece of ass like you and smell the
fumes of your sweaty ass, I'll do it.
Haha. N not because I like it or find
you sexy or anything. Haha.
>> Okay. Hey, Sky. What about you?
>> Yeah, sure. I I don't give a [__]
>> And that was how I, Sonic the Hedgehog,
saved not one but four whole universes
alongside my lover.
>> My beach, quit your deing and feed me my
$400 ruby Roman grape.
>> Flawless. Turn the TV off and come on.
Twilight wants to take a drive and maybe
rent an educational documentary from
Family Video if she's feeling risque.
>> I'm just so scared to get under and
wories
will make me fly and regret it. So I
know it's not the way it seems.
Damn, this tastes amazing.
>> Let me try it.
>> Hey, it tastes like liquid applesauce.
>> And that's only the first phase. If you
let it sit in your mouth for like 5
seconds, it tastes like an apple pie. Oh
my gosh, it does. The sugars are
interacting with the apple spice to
create an astonishing secondary layer of
flavor.
You two are really going to stand there
drinking apple juice and then get
surprised when it tastes like an apple.
But the pie note is all in your head.
You imbecile. Your brain is simply
associating the apple flavor with what
we had last week.
Make me regret inside.
>> Put the Reese's pieces back. You know I
can't afford name brand right now.
>> See anything you want to watch.
>> Hey, you know we didn't actually invite
you out here to look for a movie.
>> I wanted to talk to you.
>> Since the tournament, you've seemed
really quiet. If there's something
bothering you, you know you can always
talk to me about it. When Twilight split
me in two, she removed my dark heart,
and it made me easy for you to mold. But
I'm not as weak and docil as I was
before. I might just burn this building
to the ground right now with you two
inside. But you won't because if you do,
I might not buy you these Reese's
pieces.
I don't even know why. I know.
I don't even know why I'm trying
anymore. I'm lying on my floor. Still
wearing what I when I saw you.
I remember when you were when you were
me. But you all told me when you were
dreaming of me, but now you need much
more.
I know you need much more.
Every day is a blue sky, black sky. Now
I long for old skies. They seem never
more
roar. Feeling rainbow. I wonder
where it all went wrong. I remember when
you were mine. When you were a father of
me. When you were told me. When you
drink out of me. But now you need much
more. Oh.
But now you need much more.
Sup everyone. I'm Prince Sky, the prince
of Araon. But what a lot of people don't
know is that I'm a huge fan of Sonic
Underground. I bet you are too. If you
want to see more videos like this one,
why not join Patreon and get like some
cool gifts and [__]